<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>ICNTSE FEED</title>
  <link>http://www.icntse.com</link>
  <description>International Conference on New Trends in Sustainable Energy - PUA - KTH</description>
  <item>
	  <title>2 Prominent Egyptian Keynote Speakers Added!</title>
    <link>http://www.icntse.com/keynote.php</link>
    <description>Our prominent Egyptian keynote speakers have been added.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
	  <title>12 Prestigious KTH Keynote Speakers Added!</title>
    <link>http://www.icntse.com/keynote.php</link>
    <description>Our prestigious KTH keynote speakers have been added.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
  <item>
	  <title>Swedish Institute Sponsors ICNTSE</title>
    <link>http://www.icntse.com/home.php#sponsors</link>
    <description>ICNTSE would like to thank the Swedish Institute for contributing to the success of the conference and its sponsorship.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
	  <title>Exhibitor Registration Available</title>
    <link>http://www.icntse.com/exhibitres.php</link>
	<description>The conference would be pleased to accommodate, display and showcase your company/institution/research's exhibitions!  Please, register your name, email address and the space you would like to reserve.  You will be contacted soon after your registration.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
	  <language>ar</language>
	  <title>مؤتمر ICNTSE الآن تحت رعاية وزارة الكهرباء و الطاقة المتجددة</title>
    <link>http://www.icntse.com/news.php</link>
    <description>وزير الكهرباء و الطاقة المتجددة السيد / أ.د.محمد شاكر المرقبي قبل دعوة حضور حفل الإفتتاح و أن المؤتمر سيكون تحت رعاية وزارة الكهرباء و الطاقة المتجددة, مصر</description>
  </item>
  <item>
	  <title>ICNTSE is now under the auspices of The Ministry of Electricity and Renewable Energy - Egypt</title>
    <link>http://www.icntse.com/news.php</link>
    <description>The Minister of Electricity and Renewable Energy, Dr. Mohamed Shaker El-Markabi, has accepted the invitation to attend the conference's opening ceremony and that the conference would be under the auspices of The Ministry of Electricity and Renewable Energy - Egypt.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Updates to Fees</title>
    <link>http://www.icntse.com/fees.php</link>
    <description>Fees Updated</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Updates to Important Deadlines</title>
    <link>http://www.icntse.com/home.php#callPapers</link>
    <description>Important Deadlines Updated</description>
  </item>
</channel>

</rss>
